Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files P-T, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files A
  - Subject Files T
    - Tywoods, Gabre Amlah (Box A-119, Folder 212)
    - Tzomes, Alfonso (Chancellor) (Box A-119, Folder 213)
      Photographer if identified: US Naval Academy